[{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450203,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":18321,"timeElapsed":271675},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464724,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":14519,"timeElapsed":286196},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980478924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":14197,"timeElapsed":300396},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":25348,"timeElapsed":325746},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":16406,"timeElapsed":342155},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":16794,"timeElapsed":358953},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980556850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":19365,"timeElapsed":378322},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568490,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":11636,"timeElapsed":389962},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980589239,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"23","question":"How close and warm is your family? Do you feel your childhood was happier than most other people’s?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":20746,"timeElapsed":410711},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980605056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":12355,"timeElapsed":426528},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980613103,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8045,"timeElapsed":434575},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980621153,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8049,"timeElapsed":442625},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":13866,"timeElapsed":456493},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647544,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":12522,"timeElapsed":469016},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980663296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":15751,"timeElapsed":484768},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980677291,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":13993,"timeElapsed":498763},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980688343,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":11050,"timeElapsed":509814},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"117","question":"What did your parents teach you about love?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":10170,"timeElapsed":519987},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":13177,"timeElapsed":536055},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980720000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":5414,"timeElapsed":541472},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980726051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":6048,"timeElapsed":547523},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":14678,"timeElapsed":562203},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980749131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":8398,"timeElapsed":570603},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758431,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":9297,"timeElapsed":579903},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980773309,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14874,"timeElapsed":594780},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":14377,"timeElapsed":609160},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795978,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":8287,"timeElapsed":617450},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980806519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10539,"timeElapsed":627991},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":21626,"timeElapsed":652519},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980838068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":7019,"timeElapsed":659540},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843177,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5107,"timeElapsed":664648},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980857527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":14349,"timeElapsed":678999},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865677,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":8155,"timeElapsed":687149},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":13648,"timeElapsed":700798},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980891673,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":12344,"timeElapsed":713145},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":12268,"timeElapsed":725414},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980914656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"72","question":"Do you have one or more tattoos? If so, describe one and the reasons you got it. If not, take a few moments to describe something you might consider getting as a tattoo (or why you prefer not to have one)","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":10711,"timeElapsed":736128},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980928300,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":11227,"timeElapsed":749772},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980933756,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5454,"timeElapsed":755228},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980940719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":6961,"timeElapsed":762191},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980956410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":15690,"timeElapsed":777882},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980966047,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":9635,"timeElapsed":787519},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980974524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":8476,"timeElapsed":795996},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980982934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":8417,"timeElapsed":804406},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980993223,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10287,"timeElapsed":814695},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":7242,"timeElapsed":821938},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981007893,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"144","question":"Describe the funniest thing that ever happened to you.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7426,"timeElapsed":829365},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981035555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":25261,"timeElapsed":857027},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981052211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":16663,"timeElapsed":873683},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981067947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":15734,"timeElapsed":889419},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981078158,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":10209,"timeElapsed":899629},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981100226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":22067,"timeElapsed":921698},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981111701,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":11482,"timeElapsed":933173},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981119639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":7936,"timeElapsed":941111},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981126161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":6521,"timeElapsed":947633},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981133787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":7623,"timeElapsed":955259},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981154782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":17208,"timeElapsed":976254},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981173762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":18985,"timeElapsed":995234},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981179474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":5709,"timeElapsed":1000946},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981188655,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":9178,"timeElapsed":1010127},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981210695,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":22038,"timeElapsed":1032167},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981219430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":8732,"timeElapsed":1040902},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981229510,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":10086,"timeElapsed":1050982},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981254868,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":25354,"timeElapsed":1076340},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981264018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"197","question":"Do you wear glasses or contacts? If so, when did you first start and are you able to do any activities without them? If not, which sense (touch, sight, hearing, smell, taste) do you think is your least acute? Why do you think this?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":9147,"timeElapsed":1085490},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981280924,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14470,"timeElapsed":1102396},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981286627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5701,"timeElapsed":1108099},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981293236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":6616,"timeElapsed":1114708},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981298128,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":4890,"timeElapsed":1119600},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981301581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3451,"timeElapsed":1123053},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981313020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":11438,"timeElapsed":1134492},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981317869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4847,"timeElapsed":1139341},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981322595,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4725,"timeElapsed":1144067},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981327434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"187","question":"Do you drink caffeine during the day? What kind of caffeine do you drink? How many times a day do you have it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":4838,"timeElapsed":1148906},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981344226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":12161,"timeElapsed":1165697},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981351971,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":7752,"timeElapsed":1173443},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981357173,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":5201,"timeElapsed":1178645},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981364916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":7741,"timeElapsed":1186388},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981369494,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4576,"timeElapsed":1190965},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981374563,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":5067,"timeElapsed":1196035},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981379218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4652,"timeElapsed":1200689},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981384617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5397,"timeElapsed":1206089},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981398435,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"5","question":"When did you last sing to yourself? To someone else?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":13815,"timeElapsed":1219907},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981416689,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":14822,"timeElapsed":1238161},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981421048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":4357,"timeElapsed":1242520},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981425195,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4146,"timeElapsed":1246667},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981429334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4137,"timeElapsed":1250805},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981432949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3613,"timeElapsed":1254421},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981436616,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3664,"timeElapsed":1258088},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981440766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":4147,"timeElapsed":1262238},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981445034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4265,"timeElapsed":1266506},{"subjectID":"78fnjvxp3c","prolificID":"6724c8478f4d55dd8f258085","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b22ea86e95c572320d80","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981448930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"165","question":"Do you subscribe to any magazines or read online articles from any magazines? Which ones have you subscribed to or read regularly in the past?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3894,"timeElapsed":1270402}]